Put your hands, all over
把你的手,全部
Put your hands all over me
把你的双手全部放在我身上
Put your hands, all over
把你的手,全部
Put your hands all over me
把你的双手全部放在我身上
I can't seem to find
我好象没有找到
The pretty little face I left behind
我遗失的可爱小脸
Wandered out on the open road
在路上徘徊
Looking for a better place to call home
寻找一个更好的地方打电话回家
Gave her a place to stay
给她一个栖身的地方
And she got up and ran away
她起身跑掉
Well now I've had enough
现在我已经受够了
Her pretty little face has torn me up
她可爱的笑脸已经把我撕碎
Put your hands all over me
把你的双手全部放在我身上
Please talk to me, talk to me
请跟我说话,跟我说话
Tell me everything
告诉我一切的事情
It's gonna be alright
一切都会很好
Put your hands all over me
把你的双手全部放在我身上
Please walk with me, walk with me
请与我同行,与我同行
Love is a game you say
你说爱情是一个游戏
Play me and put me away
与我玩耍后抛弃了我
Now you've lost your mind
现在你在犹豫不决
The pretty little girl I left behind
我遗失的可爱小女孩
And now you're getting rough
现在你正处于艰难
But everybody knows you're not that tough
但是每个人都知道你没有那么坚强
Wandered out on the open road
路上徘徊
Looking for a place to call your own
寻找一个地方只为呼唤你
Scared to death of the road ahead
害怕路的前方的死亡
Pretty little thing, don't get upset
可爱的小东西,不要不安
Put your hands all over me
把你的双手全部放在我身上
Please talk to me, talk to me
请跟我说话,跟我说话
Tell me everything
告诉我一切的事情
It's gonna be alright
一切都会很好
Put your hands all over me
把你的双手全部放在我身上
Please walk with me, walk with me
请与我同行,与我同行
Love is a game you say
你说爱情是一个游戏
Play me and put me away
与我玩耍后抛弃了我
Love is a game you say
你说爱情是一个游戏
Play me and put me away
与我玩耍后抛弃了我
So come down off your cloud
所以从你的云朵上下来
Say it now
现在就说
Say it loud
大声的说
Get up in my face
在我的期盼中振作
Pretty little girl
可爱的小女孩
Come make my day
过来让我开心
Put your hands all over me
把你的双手全部放在我身上
Please talk to me, talk to me
请跟我说话,跟我说话
Put your hands all over me
把你的双手全部放在我身上
Now walk with me, walk with me now
请与我同行,与我同行
Put your hands all over me
把你的双手全部放在我身上
Gotta talk to me, talk to me
跟我说话,跟我说话
Put your hands all over me
把你的双手全部放在我身上
Gotta walk with me, walk with me
跟我说话,跟我说话
Love is a game you say
你说爱情是一个游戏
Play me and put me away
与我玩耍后抛弃了我
Love is a game you said
你说爱情是一个游戏
Play me and put me away
与我玩耍后抛弃了我
Yeah
耶~
欧耶！ 谢谢
所以 女士们 先生们
能在这里表演是一件很荣幸的事情 因为
今晚还有其他好多很棒的嘉宾在这演出
例如酷玩乐队待会会出来表演  多么棒啊
能在这里成为（音乐节）表演的一部分是多么酷啊  再说一次
非常感谢大家
剩下最后一首歌 一首 你们想听吗？
这首歌 这首歌是描述女孩的歌 现场的女孩们在哪里？
有一个漂亮、超凡、性感的女孩  这首歌讲的就是这个